A new spin on the old song and dance.
Love's Labour's Lost is a comedy, music, romance
film directed by Kenneth Branagh.
A scholarly king and his three companions swear off the society of women for three years, only to have a
diplomatic visit from a French princess and her three ladies-in-waiting thwart their intentions.
The King (Ferdinand), played by Alessandro Nivola.
The Princess, played by Alicia Silverstone.
Rosaline, played by Natascha McElhone.
Berowne, played by Kenneth Branagh.
Maria, played by Carmen Ejogo.
Longaville, played by Matthew Lillard.
Love's Labour's Lost is a 2000 British musical romantic comedy film written, directed by and
starring Kenneth Branagh, based on the comic play of the same name by William Shakespeare.
The first feature film to be made of this lesser-known comedy, Branagh's fourth film
of a Shakespeare play was a box-office and critical disappointment.
The cast includes Shakespearean veterans such as Timothy Spall, Richard Briers and Geraldine McEwan, alongside Hollywood
actors Alicia Silverstone and Matthew Lillard and Broadway and West End stars such as Nathan Lane and Jimmy Yuill.
As a result of its poor commercial performance, Miramax shelved its three-picture deal with
Branagh, who subsequently returned to Shakespeare with As You Like It in 2006.
The film explores themes of dance, musical, romance.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.